Blumen, Isadore, Files /4225
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Isadore Blumen Files
1914-1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Blumen, Isadore
/4225
2.5 cubic feet
2.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Mostly Cornell faculty meeting minutes and related material.
8055327
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Scope and Contents
Meeting minutes and related material from the Cornell Faculty Council of Representatives, University Faculty meetings, and ILR Faculty meetings. There are also two drafts for what appears to be an unpublished book, "Cornell: 1969."
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3006: ILR School Dean's Office Publications /4135 OHT: ILR School Founding Faculty Oral History Project /4138: Isadore Blumen Papers /4297: ILR School Biography Files 6047: Archives Information File
Blumen, Isadore; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8055327
- FCR (Faculty Council of Representatives) Minutes 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- University Faculty 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- FCR 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- University Faculty 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- University Faculty 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- FCR 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- University Faculty 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- FCR 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- FCR 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- University Faculty 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- University Faculty 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Affirmative Action 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Committee on Academic Integrity + Non-discrimination 1972, 1976-1977, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- A 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- B 1965-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- C 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- D 1968-1969, 1979, 1968-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- H 1966, 1970, 1971, 1978, 1966-1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- M 1962-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- P 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- R 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- S 1968, 1970-75, 1991, 1968-1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- W 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Y 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Cornell: 1969 Preface - pg. 143, copy B, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cornell: 1969 preface -pg. 144-317, copy B, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Cornell: 1969 pages 318-482, copy B, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Cornell: 1969 pages 483-672, copy B, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Cornell: 1969 Comments, copy B, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Correspondence 1968-69, 1971 Prof. Blumen, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- COSEP (Committee on Special Educational Projects) 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Faculty Council of Representatives - 1971, 1974-1975, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Committee on Independent Courses 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- University Faculty Meeting - Minutes 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Cornell: 1969 preface -pg. 143, Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Cornell: 1969 -pg. 144-317, Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Cornell: 1969 -pg. 318-482, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Cornell: 1969 -pg. 483-672, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Cornell: 1969 Comments, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
- HAP - Human Affairs Program 1974-1975, 1979, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Human Affairs Program Posters, 1974-1979 (Mapcase folder 3)
- ILR Faculty 1975-1976 folder 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ILR Faculty 1975-1976 folder 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- "A Case Study of a University's Pattern of Error,: Allan P. Sindler 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- J.H. Whitlock 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- The Quality of Faculty: A Draft document, ND (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Student Discipline and the Judiciary Systems: A draft document, ND (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Campus Disorders, A Draft Document, ND (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Memorandum of Statement by Professor Blumen to Robertson Committee, 6/7/69, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Exhibits D-K 1965-1969, 1972, 1965-1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Faculty Notices 1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Dean, University Faculty 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- ILR - Minutes, Faculty Meeting 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Interim Executive Committee 1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Faculty Council of Representatives 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Executive Committee of the FCR 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Faculty Committee for Academic Integrity 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- University Faculty Minutes 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- University Faculty Minutes 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- University Faculty Minutes 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- University Faculty Minutes 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Faculty Minutes 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Hartman, John 1968, 1972, 1975, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Murphy, R. P. Dean (Faculty Council) 1966-68, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- President James A. Perkins 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Plane, R.A. Provost 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- ROTC 1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Committee on Academic Policies + Programs 1968, 1972-1973, 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- The University Faculty 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- McPhelin Incident - Spring 1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Cornell University Board of Trustees 1969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Human Affairs Program folder 1, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 32a)
- Humans Affairs Program folder 2, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 32b)
- Independent Courses, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 33a)
- Independent Courses, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 33b)
- Carpenter (Giap-Cabral) Hall, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Memorandum of Statement by Prof. Blumen to the Robertson Committee 6/7/69, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Amalgamated Manuscripts 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Manuscripts 1939-1947 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Am. Jewish Comm. - Jews in Nazi Germany 1935 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Schlossberg Journalist Papers - General 1914-29, 1940-43, 1914-1943 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Schurman Manuscript 1926-31, 1926-1931 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Manuscripts 1935-1936 folder 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Zionism Reprints 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Arlozoloff 1928 (cassettes) (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Manuscripts 1924 (Box 6, Folder 9)